Privacy Policy for SuperRepo.org
================================

The privacy of our visitors to SuperRepo.org is important to us.

At SuperRepo.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit \_SuperRepo.org, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on SuperRepo.org to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [the privacy page of DoubleClick.com](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx "the privacy page of DoubleClick.com").

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.Opt-out for [Google Services](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) is also available. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

#### Follow us!

Have a look at our [Facebook](https://facebook.com/superrepo).

#### About SuperRepo

SuperRepo is an unofficial index for addons compatible with Kodi and XBMC. We do not maintain the addons, but make it easy to download them from within Kodi without installing a 'third party addon store'.

#### About Kodi

Kodi (formally known as XBMC) is an award-winning free and open source (GPL) software media player and entertainment hub that can be installed on Linux, OSX, Windows, iOS, and Android. [Official site of Kodi](http://kodi.tv/)

#### Support

The unofficial addons offered by SuperRepo will receive no support in official Kodi channels, including the Kodi forums and various social networks.

#### Trademark

Kodi is a registered trademark of the XBMC Foundation. We are not connected to or in any other way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.

SuperRepo is founded by Bart Otten.[Privacy Policy](https://superrepo.org/privacy-policy/)
